teslamotors.com 2010-05-26

# Tesla Motors - privacy policy

| 

We want you to get the most out of our Tesla Motors Inc. site. We recognize that privacy is an important issue, so we design and operate our services with the protection of your privacy in mind. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use our web services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it. 

### Data collection 

Tesla Motors collects limited non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. Examples of this type of data are: the name of your Internet service provider, the site that referred you to us, any pages you request, and the time and date of those requests, etc. 

There are instances where Tesla Motors requests personally identifiable information to provide site visitors with a service. This information, such as name, mailing address, email address, and type of request, is collected and stored in a manner appropriate to the nature of the request, as determined by Tesla Motors Inc, to fulfill your needs. 

For some services, we may request credit card or other payment information. Tesla Motors maintains this information in encrypted form on secure servers. 

### Cookies 

Tesla Motors may send your browser a “cookie” that uniquely identifies your browser. Your browser will store the cookie as a string of characters that will be sent back to our website to improve the user experience of our website. Many websites will not work without the use of cookies. It is possible to set your browser to reject cookies, but be aware that some web services or features of our site may not function properly. 

### Information sharing 

Personally identifiable Information collected on our website is never provided or sold to any other company for that company's independent use without your consent. 

However, we may share such information in any of the following circumstances: 

  * We have your consent. 
  * We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 
  * We conclude that we are required by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Tesla Motors, its users or the public. 

Tesla Motors may choose to process and store personal information at any of our facilities in the United States or any other country in which Tesla Motors or its agents have facilities. By providing your information, you consent to the transfer of your information among these facilities. 

In the event of a change of ownership of Tesla Motors Inc, such as a merger or acquisition with another company, we will provide notice before any personally identifying information becomes subject to a privacy policy not in compliance with this policy. 

We may share aggregated information without personally identifying information, such as the number of hits on a page, with other entities. 

### Information security 

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. 

We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. 

### Links 

Our site may link to other company sites. When you follow a link for our site, we advise you to check the privacy statements of any site before providing any personally identifiable information. 

### Changes to this Policy 

Privacy Policy will change from time to time. We do not intend to make any major revisions, but the new policy will be available on the website 7 days before it takes effect. 

If you have any additional questions, please feel free to contact us any time at [webmaster@teslamotors.com](mailto:webmaster@teslamotors.com). 

### Copyrights and Trademarks 

This site and all associated materials are protected by worldwide copyright laws and international treaty provisions. This applies whether or not a copyright notice is present on the materials. You agree to comply with all copyright laws in your use of this site and to prevent unauthorized copying of the materials. Tesla Motors Inc does not grant any express or implied rights to you under any copyrights, trademarks or patents. 

|  |
